thesoftking.com 2015-12-25

# THESOFTKING.COM - Cheap WebHosting, Reseller Hosting, Master Reseller Hosting, Alpha Reseller Hosting, VPS, BulkSMS Reseller, Cheap SMTP, Social Service, Facebook Advertising, Online Payment, Cheap Domain Reseller, Website Development, VoiceSMS System, Tower Targeted SMS Marketing, Area Targeted Voice Marketing, Radio ShoutCast Hosting, ShoutCast Reseller, Streaming Server

In an effort to protect our clients' and site visitors privacy and rights, THESOFTKING has established a Privacy Policy which explains what information we gather on visitors and what we do with information that we gather.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which THESOFTKING collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this Web site (each, a "User").

### Privacy

Users' privacy is very important to THESOFTKING. We are committed to safeguarding the information Users entrust to THESOFTKING.

### We are committed to protecting your privacy

We collect the minimum amount of information about you that is commensurate with providing you with a satisfactory service. This Policy indicates the type of processes that may result in data being collected about you. The purpose of this Privacy Policy to enable you to understand which personal identifying information ("PII", "Personal Information") of yours is collected, how and when we might use your information, who has access to this information, and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our website. 

### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer our site and servers, track access, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. It is possible that personal information about a customer may be included in the log files due to the normal functions of IP addresses and Web browsing.

### Changes to this Policy

Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be placed here and will supersede this version of our Policy. We will take reasonable steps to draw your attention to any changes in our Policy. However, to be on the safe side, we suggest that you read this document each time you use the website to ensure that it still meets with your approval.

Powered by [WHMCompleteSolution](http://www.whmcs.com/)
